Roth Isekairo
Coronavirus, there.
Crescent.
What is it? A croissant that is already tiny at other times is delicious too.
This is a very tasty croissant you can buy at Fukuoka airport.
It's because I'm up late at night.
It's because I have to stay up late at night to get to know the staff.
But lately I've been going to bed around that time.
I see.
So I thought I could get up.
I washed my clothes twice.
Every few minutes.
I chopped and poured.
He didn't wake up.
I didn't wake up.
Ugh. 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
What time did you wake up?
10:08.
Oh, no.
This is Maimi Nakamura. Please.
Don't lie about how you feel.
Thank you.
Well then, that's enough.
I feel better now that I've sorted out a lot of things.
Various families have come to my hometown,
I think some of them live in Fukuoka, or Kyoto,
I think some of them live in Fukuoka or Kyoto, and some of them are going to organize the event,
I will do my best to make them enjoy the event.
I was very happy. I was happy to be back after a long time,
I felt like I was in Fukuoka.
From the airport when I was coming to Fukuoka by plane,
"Oh, Fukuoka! Fukuoka! I had a feeling that I was in Fukuoka.
I missed you, didn't I?
I missed you so much.
What are you going to do?
It was a great experience for the five of us to do so many things on our own,
We learned a lot,
I think we will be able to show our growth in the spring tour.
I will do my best.
I'm going to drink some water.
Where are we?
Fukuoka!
We are ABC! ABC! Part-time job!
Telling Konachan calms her down.
Really? You're telling everyone that.
No, I haven't.
I was so happy that 10 of us could come to Fukuoka for the first time.
I thought there were a lot of people who live in Fukuoka or nearby who came today,
I felt like I came home.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
How was our day?
I've been meaning to say that for a long time.
I just wanted to say it up.
I like to be seen.
Your name is
Cucumber
At the end, Ema-chan's hair was through,
I was about to put it back when I decided to dry it off and say bye-bye,
I forgot I had a microphone,
I couldn't do it,
Do you understand?
Do you get it?
See you soon.